http://www.tpcu.org/index.php/privacy-policy.html

Join the Credit Union | Locations & ATMs | Contact
Online Banking
HomeAccountsSavings & InvestmentsSavings AccountsMoney MarketCertificatesChristmas ClubYouth AccountsFree CheckingDebit CardsCourtesy PayCalculatorsLoansGetting ApprovedVehicle LoansPersonal LoansHome LoansCredit CardsCalculatorsAuto CenterServicesGeneral ServicesOnline BankingMobile BankingAutomated Phone Banking
Direct DepositPayroll Deduction
InsuranceSafe Deposit Boxes
Mobile WalletResourcesCurrent PromotionsNewsletterFinancial EducationCommon Account FormsJoin The Credit UnionCredit Union HistoryAbout Shared BranchingFree Credit ReportsReorder ChecksCalculatorsRatesSavings RatesLoan RatesSchedule of Fees
HomeAccountsSavings & InvestmentsSavings AccountsMoney MarketCertificatesChristmas ClubYouth AccountsFree CheckingDebit CardsCourtesy PayCalculatorsLoansGetting ApprovedVehicle LoansPersonal LoansHome LoansCredit CardsCalculatorsAuto CenterServicesGeneral ServicesOnline BankingMobile BankingAutomated Phone Banking
Direct DepositPayroll Deduction
InsuranceSafe Deposit Boxes
Mobile WalletResourcesCurrent PromotionsNewsletterFinancial EducationCommon Account FormsJoin The Credit UnionCredit Union HistoryAbout Shared BranchingFree Credit ReportsReorder ChecksCalculatorsRatesSavings RatesLoan RatesSchedule of Fees
Privacy Policy
NOTICE OF YOUR FINANCIAL PRIVACY RIGHTS
We, our, and us, when used in this notice, mean Tampa Postal Federal Credit Union.
This is our privacy notice of our members. When we use the words “you” and “your” we mean the following types of members:
Our consumer members who have a continuing relationship by purchasing or holding financial products or services such as a(n):
Share account
Loan account
Credit card account
Mortgage brokerage services
We will tell you the sources of the information we collect about you. We will tell you what measures we take to secure that information.
We first define some terms.
Nonpublic personal information means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records. Hereafter, we will use the term “information” to mean nonpublic personal information as defined in this section.
An affiliate is a company we own or control.
A nonaffiliated third party is a person we do not employ or a company that is not an affiliate of ours. This is also known as nonaffiliated third party, or simply, an “other party.”
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect information about you from the following sources:
Information you give us on applications or other forms
Information about your transactions with us
Information about your transactions with other parties
Information from a consumer reporting agency
THE CONFIDENTIALITY, SECURITY, AND INTEGRITY OF YOUR INFORMATION
We restrict access to information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect this information.
YOUR INFORMATION AND OTHER PARTIES
We will not disclose information about you to anyone except as disclosed in this policy or as permitted by law. Examples of this might include disclosures necessary to service your account or prevent unauthorized transactions.
INFORMATION ABOUT FORMER MEMBERS
We do not disclose information about former members, except as permitted by law.
AUTHORIZED SHARING – OUTSITE MARKETING SERVICES
We may disclose the following information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf:
Information you give us on an application or other forms, such as:
Name
Address
We disclose the information listed above with companies that perform marketing services on our behalf. You do not have a right to opt out of the disclosure of this information. We may also disclose information about you to other outside marketing services as permitted by law.
Types of Businesses
Here are the types of businesses with whom we may disclose information for outside marketing purposes:
Service providers that perform marketing services, such as:
Direct sales companies
Reasons for Disclosing
We may disclose information about you to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf to provide you with information about additional products and services.
Limitations on Disclosure
Here are the limitations we impose on the use of information disclosed to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf:
We only allow direct mail solicitations.
We do not allow telephone solicitations.
Federally Insured by NCUA. Equal Housing Lender.
